GOD IS STILL SAYING SOMETHING
On Sunday 10th July, 2016, during a Sunday Live Service at The SCOAN,
Prophet T.B. Joshua gave a prophetic message regarding an attack on Thursday.
These were his words...
Since morning, God keeps saying we should pray and fast on Thursday
and avert any attack in any nation.
On Thursday, this coming Thursday, pray and fast.
I said, which nation?
I can't say this is the nation - the attack they are talking about.
But every nation, just pray on Thursday -
an attack on any nation should be averted.
So, please, open your lips and pray, right now.
On Thursday.
In Jesus Christ's name.
We cover Thursday with the blood of Jesus.
Begin to cover Thursday with the blood of Jesus.
Cover Thursday with the blood of Jesus.
In any way, cover it with the blood of Jesus.
In Jesus Christ's name!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.